http://www.petgoldfish.net/privacy-policy.html

First Poll
What is your favorite brand of goldfish food?
Second Poll
What is your favorite type of goldfish?
Privacy Policy for www.petgoldfish.net
If you require any more information or have any questions about our
privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at
.
At www.petgoldfish.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of
personal information is received and collected by www.petgoldfish.net
and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, www.petgoldfish.net makes use of log files.
The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP )
addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to help analyze
trends and administer this website. IP addresses and other such
information are not linked to any information that is personally
identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
www.petgoldfish.net does use cookies to store information about
visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages
the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors
browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their
browser.
(Basically, this just means that the forum and gallery scripts on www.petgoldfish.net use cookies that are created by a webbrowser to store a user's login information so that he/she doesn't have to relogin every few minutes. It's same thing when you visit yahoo mail or facebook, where cookies are used to store your login information for those particular websites. Other than that www.petgoldfish.net doesn't utilize cookies anywhere else).
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the
users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the
Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....
Google Adsense
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to
the advertisements and links that appear on www.petgoldfish.net send
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address
when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or
Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to
measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to
personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.petgoldfish.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these
third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices
as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.
www.petgoldfish.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot
control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your
individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie
management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers'
respective websites.
My Favorite Fish..
HOMESITEMAPGOLDFISH NAMESFACTSGOLDFISH FORUMTOPICSLINK TO USPRIVACY POLICY
